schools.org 2015-03-16

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                                                                 Rev. 11/2013
 PRIVACY
 POLICY
                                   WHAT DOES SCHOOLS FINANCIAL CREDIT UNION
 FACTS                             DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                              Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                                   consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                                   how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                                   understand what we do.
 What?                             The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                                   have with us. This information can include:
                                     • Social Security Number and account balances.
                                     • Payment history.
                                     • Credit card or other debt.
                                     • Checking account information.
                                     • Mortgage rates and payments.
                                   When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                                   notice.
 How?                              All financial companies need to share member’s personal information to run their everyday
                                   business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their member’s
                                   personal information; the reasons Schools Financial Credit Union chooses to share; and whether
                                   you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share                                           Does Schools Financial                Can you limit
your personal information                                      Credit Union share?                   this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes —
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                             Yes                                    No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes —
                                                                               Yes                                    No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                             No                             We do not share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                               No                             We do not share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness                                         No                            We do not share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                             No                             We do not share
Questions? Call 916-569-5400 (Sacramento area) or 800-962-0990 or visit schools.org.

                                                                                                                               Page 2
What we do
How does Schools       To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that
Financial Credit Union comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
protect my personal    We maintain physical, electronic and procedural controls that comply with federal regulations to guard
information?           your information.
How does Schools       We collect personal information, for example, when you:
Financial Credit Union    • Open an account or show us your government-issued ID.
collect my personal       • Apply for a loan or use your credit or debit card.
information?              • Make a deposit or withdrawal from your account.
                       We also collect personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all  Federal law gives you the rights to limit only:
sharing?                  • Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purpose — information about your creditworthiness.
                          • Affiliates from using your information to market to you.
                          • Sharing nonaffiliates to market to you.
                       State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                          • Schools Financial Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.
Nonaffiliates          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial
                       companies.
                          • Schools Financial Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products
                       or services to you.
                          • Schools Financial Credit Union does not jointly market.
Internet marketing     Our website, schools.org, uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc.
                       (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies,” or text files, placed on your computer to help analyze how
                       consumers use schools.org. The information generated by the cookie is transmitted to, stored and
                       evaluated by Google. Google may also transfer this information to third parties when required to do
                       so by law, or where third parties process the information for Google. The information generated by
                       cookies may also be aggregated and accessed by third parties who provide us with services related to
                       schools.org. By using schools.org, you consent to the processing of such data by Google and other
                       third parties in the manner and for the purposes set forth above.
                       Schools also advertises on the Internet. In doing so, we use Google to show our ads on a variety of
                       websites. Google uses cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to a website. You may opt out
                       of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. You may also refuse the use
                       of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do
                       so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Internet.
                                                                                                                        GO167 11/2013
